{
  "applicant--address-title": "%s mailing address",
  "applicant--address-description": "We’ll send any important information about this form to this address.",
  "applicant--address-label--military": "Address is on a U.S. military base outside of the United States.",
  "applicant--address-label--street3": "Apartment or unit number",
  "applicant--address-change-label": "Has the beneficiary’s mailing address changed since their last CHAMPVA form submission?",
  "applicant--address-change-hint": "Any updates you make here will only apply to your CHAMPVA benefits. We won’t update your address in your VA.gov profile.",
  "applicant--age-title": "%s age",
  "applicant--age-label": "Is the beneficiary 65 years old or older?",
  "applicant--age-hint": "Depending on your response, you may need to submit additional documents.",
  "applicant--age-option--yes": "Yes, the beneficiary is 65 or older",
  "applicant--age-option--no": "No, the beneficiary is under 65",
  "applicant--birth-sex-title": "%s sex listed at birth",
  "applicant--birth-sex-label": "What’s the beneficiary’s sex listed at birth?",
  "applicant--birth-sex-hint": "Enter the sex that appears on the beneficiary’s birth certificate.",
  "applicant--contact-info-title": "%s contact information",
  "applicant--identity-info-title": "%s identification information",
  "applicant--name-title": "%s name",
  "arraybuilder--button-cancel-no": "No, continue",
  "arraybuilder--button-cancel-yes": "Yes, cancel",
  "arraybuilder--button-delete-no": "No, keep",
  "arraybuilder--button-delete-yes": "Yes, delete",
  "attachments--button-text": "Upload file",
  "attachments--hint-text": "Upload front and back as separate files.",
  "dates--default-label": "Date",
  "form--option--yes": "Yes",
  "form--option--no": "No",
  "form--option--unsure": "I’m not sure",
  "health-insurance--cancel-add-title": "Cancel adding this plan?",
  "health-insurance--cancel-add-description": "If you cancel adding this plan, we won’t save its information. You’ll return to a screen where you can add or remove plans.",
  "health-insurance--cancel-edit-item-title": "Cancel editing %s’s information?",
  "health-insurance--cancel-edit-noun-title": "Cancel editing this %s information?",
  "health-insurance--cancel-edit-description": "If you cancel editing this health insurance plan, we won’t save its information. You’ll return to a screen where you can add or remove other health insurance policies.",
  "health-insurance--delete-item-description": "This will delete %s and all the information from your list of other health insurance plans.",
  "health-insurance--delete-noun-description": "This will delete this %s and all the information from your list of other health insurance plans.",
  "health-insurance--summary-title": "Review other health insurance",
  "health-insurance--summary-title--review": "Other health insurance plans",
  "health-insurance--summary-title-no-items": "Report health insurance",
  "health-insurance--summary-date-present": "present",
  "health-insurance--summary-date-missing": "Not specified",
  "health-insurance--yes-no-title": "Does the beneficiary need to add or update other health insurance information?",
  "health-insurance--yes-no-more-title": "Do you have any other health insurance to report?",
  "health-insurance--yes-no-hint": "If so, you must report this information for us to process your application.",
  "health-insurance--addtl-comments-title": "%s health insurance additional comments",
  "health-insurance--addtl-comments-title--review": "Additional comments",
  "health-insurance--addtl-comments-label": "Do you have any additional comments about the beneficiary’s health insurance?",
  "health-insurance--addtl-comments-hint": "Use this space to let us know about any upcoming changes in the insurance coverage you added.",
  "health-insurance--card-upload-title": "Upload %s health insurance card",
  "health-insurance--card-upload-title--review": "Health insurance card",
  "health-insurance--card-upload-description": "You’ll need to submit a copy of the front and back of this health insurance card.",
  "health-insurance--card-upload-label--front": "Upload front of the health insurance card",
  "health-insurance--card-upload-label--back": "Upload back of the health insurance card",
  "health-insurance--employer-title": "Type of insurance for %s",
  "health-insurance--employer-title--review": "Employer sponsorship",
  "health-insurance--employer-label": "Is this insurance through the beneficiary’s employer?",
  "health-insurance--medigap-title": "Medigap information",
  "health-insurance--medigap-label": "Select the Medigap policy the beneficiary is enrolled in",
  "health-insurance--medigap-option-text": "Medigap Plan",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-title": "Private or employer-sponsored insurance plan",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-label": "Which type of insurance plan or program is the beneficiary enrolled in?",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-hint": "This information is on the front of your health insurance card.",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-option--hmo": "Health Maintenance Organization (HMO) program",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-option--ppo": "Preferred Provider Organization (PPO) plan",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-option--medicaid": "Medicaid or a state assistance program",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-option--medigap": "Medigap policy",
  "health-insurance--plan-type-option--other": "Other (specialty, limited coverage, or exclusively CHAMPVA supplemental) insurance",
  "health-insurance--prescription-title": "%s prescription coverage",
  "health-insurance--prescription-title--review": "Prescription coverage",
  "health-insurance--prescription-label": "Does the beneficiary’s health insurance cover prescriptions?",
  "health-insurance--prescription-hint": "You may find this information on the front of the health insurance card. You can also contact the phone number listed on the back of the card.",
  "health-insurance--provider-title": "Health insurance information",
  "health-insurance--provider-label": "Name of insurance provider",
  "health-insurance--effective-date-label": "Insurance start date",
  "health-insurance--effective-date-hint": "This information is on the insurance policy declarations page.",
  "health-insurance--termination-date-label": "Insurance termination date",
  "health-insurance--termination-date-hint": "Only enter this date if the policy is inactive.",
  "medicare--card-sample-title": "Sample of Original Medicare card",
  "medicare--card-sample-label--front": "Front of card",
  "medicare--card-sample-label--back": "Back of card",
  "medicare--card-upload-alt-text--back": "Back of a red, white, and blue Medicare card. Includes card usage instructions and the Medicare phone number and website.",
  "medicare--carrier-label": "Name of insurance carrier",
  "medicare--carrier-hint": "The insurance carrier may be listed as “Medicare Health Insurance” on the insurance card.",
  "medicare--carrier-hint--alt": "This is the name of the insurance company.",
  "medicare--effective-date-label": "Effective date",
  "medicare--general-pharmacy-title": "%s Medicare pharmacy benefits",
  "medicare--general-pharmacy-label": "Does the beneficiary’s Medicare plan provide pharmacy benefits?",
  "medicare--general-pharmacy-hint": "You can find this information on the front of the Medicare card.",
  "medicare--intro-title": "Report Medicare",
  "medicare--mbi-title": "%s MBI",
  "medicare--mbi-description": "Every Medicare recipient has an 11-character Medicare Beneficiary Identifier (MBI) code. You can find this code on the front of Medicare cards or on medicare.gov accounts.",
  "medicare--mbi-label": "MBI",
  "medicare--mbi-hint": "You can enter an HICN if that’s what’s shown on the Medicare card.",
  "medicare--parts-ab-card-title": "Upload Medicare card for Hospital and Medical insurance",
  "medicare--parts-ab-card-label--front": "Upload front of Original Medicare card",
  "medicare--parts-ab-card-label--back": "Upload back of Original Medicare card",
  "medicare--parts-ab-card-alt-text--front": "Red, white, and blue Medicare card. It states “Medicare Health Insurance” and lists the Medicare number and coverage dates for Part A hospital and Part B medical coverage.",
  "medicare--parts-ab-effective-date-title": "%s Medicare effective dates",
  "medicare--part-a-card-title": "Upload Medicare Part A card",
  "medicare--part-a-card-label--front": "Upload front of Part A Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-a-card-label--back": "Upload back of Part A Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-a-card-alt-text--front": "Red, white, and blue Medicare card. It states “Medicare Health Insurance” and lists the Medicare number and coverage dates for Part A hospital coverage.",
  "medicare--part-a-carrier-title": "%s Medicare Part A carrier",
  "medicare--part-a-denial-notice-title": "%s Medicare status",
  "medicare--part-a-denial-notice-label": "Does the beneficiary have a notice of disallowance, denial, or other proof of ineligibility for Medicare Part A?",
  "medicare--part-a-denial-notice-hint": "Depending on your response, you may need to submit additional documents.",
  "medicare--part-a-denial-proof-title": "Upload proof of Medicare ineligibility",
  "medicare--part-a-effective-date-title": "%s Medicare Part A effective date",
  "medicare--part-a-effective-date-label": "Medicare Part A effective date",
  "medicare--part-a-effective-date-hint": "You may find the effective date on the front of the Medicare card near “Coverage starts” or “Effective date.”",
  "medicare--part-a-subtitle": "Medicare Part A",
  "medicare--part-b-card-title": "Upload Medicare Part B card",
  "medicare--part-b-card-label--front": "Upload front of Part B Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-b-card-label--back": "Upload back of Part B Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-b-card-alt-text--front": "Red, white, and blue Medicare card. It states “Medicare Health Insurance” and lists the Medicare number and coverage dates for Part B medical coverage.",
  "medicare--part-b-carrier-title": "%s Medicare Part B carrier",
  "medicare--part-b-effective-date-title": "%s Medicare Part B effective date",
  "medicare--part-b-effective-date-label": "Medicare Part B effective date",
  "medicare--part-b-effective-date-hint": "This will be on the front of the Medicare card near “Coverage starts.”",
  "medicare--part-b-subtitle": "Medicare Part B",
  "medicare--part-c-card-title": "Upload Medicare Part C card",
  "medicare--part-c-card-description": "You’ll need to submit a copy of the front and back of the beneficiary’s Medicare Part C (Medicare Advantage Plan) card.",
  "medicare--part-c-card-label--front": "Upload front of Part C Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-c-card-label--back": "Upload back of Part C Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-c-carrier-title": "%s Medicare Part C carrier and effective date",
  "medicare--part-c-effective-date-label": "Medicare Part C effective date",
  "medicare--part-c-effective-date-hint": "This information is on the front of the Medicare card near “Effective date” or “Issue date.” If it’s not there, it may be on the plan’s online portal or enrollment documents.",
  "medicare--part-d-card-title": "Upload Medicare Part D card",
  "medicare--part-d-card-description": "You’ll need to submit a copy of the front and back of the beneficiary’s Medicare Part D card.",
  "medicare--part-d-card-label--front": "Upload front of Part D Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-d-card-label--back": "Upload back of Part D Medicare card",
  "medicare--part-d-carrier-title": "%s Medicare Part D carrier",
  "medicare--part-d-effective-date-title": "%s Medicare Part D effective date",
  "medicare--part-d-effective-date-label": "Medicare Part D effective date",
  "medicare--part-d-effective-date-hint": "This information is at the top of the card.",
  "medicare--part-d-status-title": "%s Medicare Part D status",
  "medicare--part-d-status-label": "Does the beneficiary have Medicare Part D information to provide or update at this time?",
  "medicare--part-d-termination-date-label": "Medicare Part D termination date",
  "medicare--part-d-termination-date-hint": "Only enter this date if the plan is inactive.",
  "medicare--plan-type-title": "%s Medicare plan types",
  "medicare--plan-type-label": "Which Medicare plan does the beneficiary have?",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--ab": "Original Medicare Parts A and B (Hospital and Medical Insurance)",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--a": "Medicare Part A only (Hospital Insurance)",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--b": "Medicare Part B only (Medical Insurance)",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--c": "Medicare Part C, also known as Medicare Advantage (includes previous enrollment in Part A and B)",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--advantage": "Medicare Advantage Plan (Part C)",
  "medicare--plan-type-option--other": "Other Medicare plan",
  "medicare--report-plan-title": "Report Medicare Plans",
  "medicare--report-plan-label": "Does the beneficiary have Medicare information to provide or update at this time?",
  "noun--your": "Your",
  "noun--beneficiary": "Beneficiary",
  "signer--benefit-status-title": "%s CHAMPVA benefit status",
  "signer--benefit-status-label": "Does the beneficiary receive CHAMPVA benefits now?",
  "signer--email-title": "Your email address",
  "signer--role-title": "Your information",
  "signer--role-label": "Which of these best describes you?",
  "signer--role-option--applicant": "I’m filling out this form for myself",
  "signer--role-option--other": "I’m a parent, spouse, or legal representative signing on behalf of the beneficiary",
  "statement-of-truth--default": "I confirm that the identifying information in this form is accurate and has been represented correctly.",
  "statement-of-truth--representative": "On behalf of %s, I confirm that the identifying information in this form is accurate and has been represented correctly.",
  "validation--date-pattern": "Enter a valid date",
  "validation--date-range": "Termination date must be after the effective date",
  "validation--date-value--current": "Enter a valid current or past date",
  "validation--date-value--future": "Date may not be more than 1 year from today",
  "validation--mbi-invalid": "Enter a valid 11-character MBI code (without dashes)",
  "validation--required": "You must provide a response",
  "validation--sot--applicant-signature": "Enter your name exactly as it appears on your application: %s",
  "validation--sot--other-signature": "Enter your full name",
  "validation--sot--checkbox": "You must certify by checking the box",
  "validation--text-characters--singular": "You entered a character we can’t accept. Try removing this character",
  "validation--text-characters--plural": "You entered multiple characters we can’t accept. Try removing these characters"
}
